David Soren popular sheet music collection, 1839-1974
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Sheet Music
  - Our Glorious Banner, 1901 Santlemann, Wm.H. Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Out Where the West Begins, 1917 Philleo, Estelle Composer Chapman, Arthur Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Over Here, 1917 Weston, Charles B. Composer Weston, Charles B. Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Over There (Three Copies), 1917 Cohan, George M. Composer Cohan, George M. Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Paris in the Spring, 1935 Gordon, Mack, Revel, Harry Composer Gordon, Mack, Revel, Harry Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Patience Lancers (From Popular Dances Old And New), 1882 Sawyer, J.J. Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Pavane, 1886 Stetson, Nahum Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Pick a Little Four Leaf Clover (and Send it Over to Me), 1918 Olman, Abe Composer Reisner, C. Francis, Rose, Ed. Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Piff! Paff! Pouf!, 1904 Schwartz, Jean Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Please Save the Last Dance for Me, 1905 Freeman, Harry Composer O’Keefe, Jack Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Please Touch My Daddy’s Star Again and Change it Back to Blue, 1918 Brandon, Clarence Composer Phelps, Marion Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Poor Pauline, 1914 Walker, Raymond Composer McCarron, Chas. Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Poppy-Time in Old Japan, 1915 Dulmage, Will E. Composer Meyers, Ernest J. Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Popular Songs (Magazine), 1934 Various Composer Various Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Pretty Girl is Like A Melody, A (From There's No Business Like Show Business), 1919 Berlin, Irving Composer Berlin, Irving Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Queen of My Dreams, 1905 Nathan, Joe Composer Overin, Douglass Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Ragtime Cowboy Joe, 1939 Muir, Lewis F., Abrahams, Maurice Composer Clarke, Grant Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Ragtime Soldier Man, The, 1912 Berlin, Irving Composer Berlin, Irving Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Ramona, 1927 Wayne, Mabel Composer Gilbert, L. Wolfe Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Rendezvous With A Dream, 1936 Robin, Leo, Rainger, Ralph Composer Robin, Leo, Rainger, Ralph Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Return of Spring Polka Brilliant, 1881 Moelling, Theo. Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Return, The, 1882 Gobbaerts, L. Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Revelry, 1899 Nall, Ollie Foster Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Riders in the Sky, 1954 Jones, Stan Composer Jones, Stan Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Rio Rita, 1926 Tierney, Harry Composer McCarthy, Joseph Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Road to Slumberland, The, 1927 Aiello, Joseph Composer D'Auvergne, Yvette Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Rock’d in the Cradle of the Deep (Sponsored by Bromo-Seltzer), undated Knight, J.P. Composer Knight, J.P. Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Rookies March, The, 1917 Drumm, George Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Rose That Bloomed Unseen, A, 1913 Chapman, Elmer B. Composer Taylor, Tell Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Ruby March (From Alabama Boys and Girls, A Choice Set of Teaching Pieces), 1912 Story, Pauline B. Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Rum and Coca-Cola, 1944 Sullavan, Jeri, Baron, Paul Composer Amsterdam, Morey Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Salut A Pesth (Marche Hongroise), 1908 Kowalski, Henri Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Senora Waltzes, 1908 Nathan, Jos. S. Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Shall I Ever See My Mother’s Face Again?, 1895 Adriance, Paul Composer Adriance, Paul Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - She Waits by the Deep Blue Sea, 1905 Morse, Theodore Composer Madden, Edward Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - She Was Just A Sailor’s Sweetheart, 1915 Burke, Joe Composer Burke, Joe Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - She’s the Daughter of Mother Machree, 1915 Ball, Ernest R. Composer Nenarb, Jeff T. Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Shepherd’s Evening Song, The, 1874 Blake, Chas. D. Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Shuffle off to Buffalo (From Forty Second Street), 1932 Warren, Harry Composer Dubin, Al Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Sing Me ‘The Rosary’ The Sweetest Song of All, 1913 Klickmann, F. Henri Composer Lewis, Roger Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Sing Me a Song of the Islands, 1942 Gordon, Mack, Owens, Harry Composer Gordon, Mack, Owens, Harry Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Sittin’ And Whittlin’, 1928 Sanders, Joe Composer Sanders, Joe Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Sleepy Head, 1934 Donaldson, Walter Composer Kahn, Gus Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Sleepy Town Express, The, 1930 Gillespie, Haven Composer Gillespie, Haven Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Sleepy Valley, 1929 Hanley, James F. Composer Sterling, Andrew B. Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Smarty, 1908 Von Tilzer, Albert Composer Norworth, Jack Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Smoke Gets in Your Eyes, 1931 Kern, Jerome Composer Harbach, Otto Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - So is your old lady, 1926 Burke, Joe Composer Durbin, Al Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - So Long, Mother, 1917 Van Alstyne, Egbert Composer Kahn, Gus, Egan, Raymond Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Some Day Your Thoughts Will Wander, 1908 Smith, C. Jay Composer Smith, C. Jay Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Someday Somewhere, 1917 Becker, Alice May Composer Becker, Alice May Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Someday, I'll Meet You Again, 1954 Sterner, Max Composer Washington, Ned Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Something Else Seems Tingle-ingleing (Cover Only), undated Hauerbach, Friml Composer Hauerbach, Friml Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Somewhere in France is the Lily (Two Copies), 1917 Howard, Joseph E. Composer Johnson, Philander Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Somewhere in the Night, 1946 Myrow, Josef Composer Gordon, Mack Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Song Hit Folio, V. 3, No. 7, undated Various Composer Various Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Songs of the Sunny South (Various Songs), undated Various Composer Various Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Soon, 1935 Rodgers, Richard Composer Hart, Lorenz Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Sounds from the Ringing Rocks, undated Walters, B. Frank Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Spirit of the U.S.A., The, 1918 Edouard, Emil, Miller, Chas. Composer La Pierre, Louise (Translator) Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Spring Greeting, undated Espen, Theodor Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Sprinkle Me With Kisses If You Want My Love to Grow, 1915 Ball, Ernest R. Composer Carroll, Earl Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Stars and Stripes Forever, The, 1897 Sousa, John Philip Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Stolen Kisses, 1886 Schleiffarth, Geo. Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Stranger in Paradise, 1953 Wright, Robert, Forrest, George Composer Wright, Robert, Forrest, George Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Sweet Dreams, My Love, Sweet Dreams, 1909 Edwards, Ed. Composer Longbrake, Arthur Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Sweeter Than All the Roses, 1896 Verner, H.C. Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Sweetest Singer, The, undated Roeckel, J.L. Composer Roeckel, J.L. Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Sweetheart Darlin', 1933 Stothart, Herbert Composer Kahn, Gus Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Sycamore Schottische, 1866 Kehr, C.H. Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Take Back the Heart (Sponsored by Bromo-Seltzer), undated Claribel Composer Claribel Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Tam O’Shanter, 1882 William, George Wm. Composer No Lyrics (Based on Poem by Robert Burns) Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Tango de Yango Dance, 1913 McCabe, Jas. C. Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Taxi, 1919 Kaufman, Mel B. Composer Kerr, Harry D. Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Tell Me Once Again You Love Me, 1905 Bowers, Frederick V. Composer Horwitz, Charles Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Ten Pin Galop, 1882 Zikoff, Fr. Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - That International Rag, 1913 Berlin, Irving Composer Berlin, Irving Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - That Soothing Serenade was Just Written for Me, 1918 De Costa, Harry Composer De Costa, Harry Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - There’s a Little Blue Star in the Window and it Means all the World to Me, 1918 Klickmann, F. Henri Composer Armstrong, Paul B. Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - There’s a Quaker down in Quaker Town, 1916 Solman, Alfred Composer Berg, David Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - There'll Be Blue Birds Over the White Cliffs of Dover, 1951 Kent, Walter Composer Burton, Nat Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - They Made it Twice as Nice as Paradise and They Called it Dixieland, 1916 Whiting, Richard A. Composer Egan, Raymond Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - They Were All Out of Step But Jim, 1918 Berlin, Irving Composer Berlin, Irving Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - This is Always, 1946 Warren, Harry Composer Gordon, Mack Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Three Fishers Went Sailing (From Fireside Favorites), undated Hullah, John Composer Kingsley, Rev. Chas. Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Three Wonderful Letters From Home (Two Copies), 1918 Hanley, James F. Composer Goodwin, Joe, MacDonald, Ballard Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Tip-top Tipperary Mary, 1914 Carroll, Harry Composer MacDonald, Ballard Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Tom Dooley, 1947 Warner, Frank, Lomax, John A., Lomax, Alan Composer Warner, Frank, Lomax, John A., Lomax, Alan Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Tres Moutarde. (Too Much Mustard), 1911 Macklin, Cecil Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Twelfth Regiment, The, 1918 Lincoln, Harry, J. Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Two Little Eyes Are Watching for a Daddy Far Away, 1918 Weasner, H.C. Composer Weasner, H.C. Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Two Little Sailor Boys, 1906 Jardon, Dolly Composer Madden, Edward Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - U.S.S. New York March, 1915 Shannon, J.R. Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - U.S.S. New York March, 1915 Shannon, J.R. Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Uncle Sam March, 1916 Noonan, Bell, D. Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Waiting at the Church; or, My Wife Won’t Let Me. (From Vesta Victoria’s New Song Successes), 1906 Pether, Henry E. Composer Leigh, Fred W. Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Warrior Bold, A (Sponsored by Bromo-Seltzer), undated Adams, Stephen Composer Thomas, Edwin Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Watch Hope and Wait Little Girl ‘I’m Coming Back to You’ (Two Copies), 1918 Clayton, Will Composer Brown, Lew Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Way You Look To-Night, The, 1936 Kern, Jerome Composer Fields, Dorothy Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - We Don’t Want The Bacon - What We Want is a Piece of the Rhine! (Two Copies), 1918 Carr, Howard, Russell, Harry, Havens, Jimmie Composer Carr, Howard, Russell, Harry, Havens, Jimmie Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - We’ll Do Our Share (While You’re Over There), 1918 Egan, Jack Composer Brown, Lew, Harriman, Al Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - We’ll Have A Jubilee In My Old Kentucky Home, 1915 Donaldson, Walter Composer Goetz, Coleman Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - We’ll Knock the Heligo-Into Heligo Out of Heligoland!, 1917 Morse, Theodore Composer O’Brien, John Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - We’re All With You Dear America, 1917 Schaeffer, Lew, Leventhal, Phil Composer Schaeffer, Lew, Leventhal, Phil Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - We’re Going Over (Two Copies), 1917 Sterling, Andrew B.; Grossman, Bernie, Lange, Arthur Composer Sterling, Andrew B.; Grossman, Bernie, Lange, Arthur Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - We’ve Kept the Golden Rule, 1910 Wenrich, Percy Composer Deely, Ben Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Weep No More My Mammy, 1921 Pollack, Lew Composer Clare, Sidney, Mitchell, Sidney D. Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - What’s the Matter with Father, 1910 Van Alstyne, Egbert, Williams, Harry Composer Van Alstyne, Egbert, Williams, Harry Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - When A Boy Says Good Bye to His Mother and She Gives Him to Uncle Sam, 1917 Frost, Jack Composer Frost, Jack Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - When I Dream of Old Erin (I’m Dreaming of You), 1912 Friedman, Leo Composer Lee, Marvin Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - When I Hear the Songs of Dixie Land, 1913 Pratt, Paul C. Composer Callahan, J.Will Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - When I Was a Dreamer and Your Were My Dream, 1914 Van Alstyne, Egbert Composer Lewis, Roger, Little, Geo. A. Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - When My Dream Boat Comes Home, 1936 Friend, Cliff, Franklin, Dave Composer Friend, Cliff, Franklin, Dave Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - When My Dreams Come True, 1929 Berlin, Irving Composer Berlin, Irving Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - When That Midnight Choo, Choo, Leaves for Alabam’, 1912 Berlin, Irving Composer Berlin, Irving Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - When the Dew is on the Rose, 1911 Owen, Anita Composer Owen, Anita Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - When the Golden Leaves are Falling, 1911 Harris, Chas. K. Composer Harris, Chas. K. Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - When You Come Back, And You Will Come Back, There’s The Whole World Waiting for You, 1918 Cohan, George Composer Cohan, George Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Where Do We Go From Here (Two Copies), 1917 Johnson, Howard, Wenrich, Percy Composer Johnson, Howard, Wenrich, Percy Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Whispering Wind, The, 1884 Wollenhaupt, H.A. Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Who are You With To-night?, 1910 Van Alstyne, Egbert Composer Williams, Harry Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Who Cares?, 1922 Ager, Milton Composer Yellen, Jack Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Whole World is Calling You, The, 1917 Anthony, Clifton S., Company B Composer Anthony, Clifton S., Company B Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Will You Remember (Sweetheart), 1917 Romberg, Sigmund Composer Young, Rida Johnson Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Windy Nebraska Waltz, 1900 Miller, Miss Nellie Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Woodland Echoes, 1908 Wyman, A.P. Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Yaaka Hula Hickey Dula, 1916 Goetz, E. Ray; Young, Joe, Wendling, Pete Composer Goetz, E. Ray; Young, Joe, Wendling, Pete Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - You Aint Got the Girl ‘Till the Ring is on Her Finger (and Even Then you Never Can Tell), 1910 Kendis, Paley Composer Bryan, Alfred Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - You Were Meant for Me (Two Copies), 1929 Brown, Nacio Herb Composer Freed, Arthur Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - You’re Not A Bit Older To-day, 1905 Eltrym, Brooke Composer Branen, Jeff T. Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - You'll Always be the One I Love (Two Copies), 1946 Freeman, Ticker Composer Skylar, Sunny Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - You're Just Like A Dream (And I Hate to Say Good-Night), 1932 Kugler, Johnny, Miller, Roy Composer Kugler, Johnny, Miller, Roy Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Yours and Mine, 1937 Brown, Nacio Herb Composer Freed, Arthur Lyricist (Box 3, Folder 11)